Guide to the Elayne Zalis video studies archive, [circa 1979-1997].
Zalis, Elayne video studies archive
- Series III. Alphabetic Subject Files
  - Asian Cinevision (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Asian Cinevision Pamphlet, 1989
    - Cinevue, Vol. IV, No. 4, December 1989
    - 12th Asian American International Film Festival Program, 1989
    - 13th Asian American International Film Festival Program, 1990
    - Voice Newspaper Article “Great Leap Forward”, 1991
  - Bay Area Video Coalition (BAVC) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Video Networks Rate Sheet 1986
    - Video Networks Rate Sheet 1989
    - Membership Invoice 1990
    - Membership Welcome Letter 1990
    - James D. Phelan Art Award in Video Call of Entries 1990
    - Video Networks Newsletter April/May 1989
    - Video Networks Newsletter February/March 1990
    - Video Networks Newsletter April/May 1990
    - Video Networks Newsletter June/July 1990
    - Video Networks Newsletter August/September 1990
    - Video Networks Newsletter December/January 1991/1992
    - Video Networks Newsletter April/May 1994
    - Video Production and Technical Workshop Schedule Spring 1990
    - Video Production and Technical Workshop Schedule Summer 1990
    - Video Production and Technical Workshop Schedule Fall 1990
  - Black Film Institute (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Black Music on Film Program Guide
    - Black Film Times 3 Program Guide 1989
    - Black Film Review Magazine Vol. 5, No. 4 1990
  - Black Filmmaker Foundation (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Black Filmmaker Foundation Membership Application 1990
  - Black Mountain College (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Spring Session Pamphlet 1989
  - Book Publishers (misc.) (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Index of Book Publishers, excerpts from ‘Literary Market Place: The Directory of American Book Publishing’ R. R. Bowker Co., NY, 1986
  - Boston Film/Video Foundation (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Visions Publication, Vol. 12, Winter 1988/1989 (2 copies)
    - Workshops Catalog, Winter/Spring 1989
    - Workshops Catalog, Summer 1989
    - Workshops Catalog, Fall 1989
    - Workshops Catalog, Winter/Spring 1990
    - Winter Exhibition Series Program, 1989
    - Accessible Equipment Pamphlet, 1989
    - Equipment Membership Application, 1989
    - Volunteer/Intern Description, 1989
    - Membership Application, 1989 (2 copies)
    - Membership Application, 1990
    - New England Film/Video Fellowship Program Application, 1990
  - Bronx Museum of the Arts (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Call to Media Artists for Exhibit “Emerging Expressions: The Third Dimension and Beyond” July 1990 (2 copies)
    - Press Kit, “Visions of Home: Designs for Affordable Housing in the Bronx” 1990 Includes: Press Release for Visions of Home, Press Release for Winners of 1990 Architechtural Design Competition, Press Release for Public Programming, Press Release Bronx Museum Fact Sheet, Press Release for ‘Home: A Place in the World”, Public Programs Brochure, ‘Visions of Home’ Postcard, ‘Visions of Home’ Proposal Guidelines, Photograph of ‘Visions of Home’ 1st Prize Winner, Photograph of ‘Visions of Home’ 3rd Prize Winner, ‘Home: A Place in the World’ Exhibition Schedule, Fall/Winter Museum Bulletin
  - Brooklyn Academy of Music (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Annual Report 1984-1985
    - American Arts Magazine Article “Calculating Risks: The Man Behind BAM”, Interview with Harvey Lichtenstein, March 1984-1985
    - New York Times Article, “BAM is a Mecca of the New”, October 1985
    - On The Next Wave Magazine, Vol. 1, No. 1, October 1983
    - On The Next Wave Magazine, Vol. 2, No. 4, December 1984
    - On The Next Wave Magazine, Vol. 3, No. 1-2, October 1985
    - On The Next Wave Magazine, Vol. 3, No. 3, November 1985
  - Brooklyn Museum (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Annual Report 1984-1985
    - ‘From This Side of the Bridge: Video in Brooklyn” Exhibition Brochure, 1990
    - AFI Video Festival New York Reprise Schedule, 1989
    - AIDS Awareness Day Video Program, 1989
    - Video 101 Public Program Brochure, 1989
    - ‘African-American Video Visions’ Exibition Brochure, 1990
    - ‘African-American Video Visions’, Program Notes on ‘Identity’, April 6, 1990
    - ‘African-American Video Visions’, Program Notes on ‘Reflections on Civil Rights’ April 1990
    - ‘African-American Video Visions’, Program Notes on ‘Documentaries on Women in the Performing Arts’ May 1990
    - ‘African-American Video Visions’, Program Notes on ‘Africa and the Diaspora’, May 1990
    - ‘African-American Video Visions’, Program Notes on ‘Philip Mallory Jones Retrospective’, May 1990
    - ‘African-American Video Visions’, Program Notes on ‘Cultural Expressions’, June 1990
  - California Video (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - RAD Satellite Network Press Release Packet, 1986
    - ‘Art in Outerspace’ Descriptioon and Artist Index
    - The Zone Show Contributing Artist Index, 1986
  - Calle, Sophie (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Bay Press Critical Texts Brochure, 1988
    - Bay Press ‘Suite venitienne/ Please follow me’ Order Form, 1988
  - Castelli/ Sonnabend Tapes and Films (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Video and Film Distribution List 1987
  - The Contemporary Art Television Fund (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - The Boston Globe article, ‘First CAT Fund tapes start unreeling tonight’, November 1984
    - The WGBH Dial article, ‘The CAT Fund: On the Cutting Edge of Video Art’ November 1984
    - The CAT Fund Presents: Broadcast Schedule, 1985
    - The CAT Fund Presents: Broadcast Schedule, 1986
    - ‘The Damnation of Faust: Will-O-The Wisp (A Deceitful Goal)’ Program Notes, 1985
    - ‘Irony’ Program Notes, 1985
    - ‘I Do Not Know What It Is I Am Like’ Program Notes, 1986
    - ‘As if memories could deceive me.’ Exhibition Brochure, 1986
    - High Performance article, ‘Video and Television’, 1986
    - AFTERIMAGE article, ‘Reigning Cats’, 1986
    - The CAT Fund Production Index, 1987
    - The CAT Fund Distribution Flyer, 1987
    - The CAT Fund: The First Five Years Catalog, 1988
    - ICA Internship Application
  - Censorship (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Letter to the Field, ‘Creative Time Will Not Sign NEA Grant Contracts Totaling $70, 000 for 1900 With Restrictive Langauge”, 1990
    - National Campagin for Freedom of Expression Donation Recept, 1990
  - Center for New Television (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Technical Facilities Rate Card, 1986
    - Technical Facilities Rate Card, 1987
    - Media Arts Facility Advertisement, 1987
    - ‘The New Media Project’ Seminar Schedule, 1987
    - SCAN Newsletter, May/June 1987
    - VIDEO Workshops Schedule, Summer 1987
    - VIDEO Workshops Schedule, Winter/Spring 1990
    - VIDEO Newsletter, November/December 1990
    - Call for Entries: The Center for New Television Regional Fellowship Program, 1987
    - Call for Entries: The Center for New Television Regional Fellowship Program, 1990
    - Call for Entries: Retirement Research Foundation National Media Awards, 1990
  - Chicago International Film Festival (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - The 26th Chicago International Film Festival Official Regulations and Entry Forms, 1990 (2 copies)
    - The 26th Chicago International Film Festival Final Call For Entries, 1990
    - The 26th Chicago International Film Festival Schedule and Guide, 1990 (2 copies)
  - The Collective for Living Cinema (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Programming Schedule, Winter 1990
    - Programming Schedule, Spring 1990
    - Magazine Covers published by The Collective for Living Cinema,1982-1990 Includes: 10 Years of Living Cinema, 1982; Motion Picture Vol. 1 No.2, Fall 1986; Motion Picture Vol. 1 No. 3, Winter/Spring 1987; Motion Picture Vol. 2, No. 1, Fall 1987, Motion Picture Vol. 3, No. 1-2, Winter 1989-1990
    - Motion Picture Vol. 3, No. 1-2, Winter 1989-1990
  - Complex Corporation (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - John Jost Film Distribution Index, 1990
    - ‘slow moves’ Flyer, 1983 Includes critical reviews from the New York Times and LA Weekly.
    - ‘Speaking Directly’ Flyer, 1973;On Back: ‘Plain Talk and Common Senses (uncommon senses)’, 1987
    - ‘Last Chants for a Slow Dance (Dead End)’ Flyer, 1977; On Back: ‘Chameleon’, 1978
    - ‘Angel City’ Flyer, 1977; On Back: ‘Stagefright’, 1981
    - ‘Bell Diamond’ by John Jost, Folio, 1986Includes critical reviews from the Chicago Reader, Newsday, Film Comment, Bay Guardian, and Christian Science Monitor.
    - ‘Uncommon Senses’ an essay by John Jost, Folio, 1987Includes critical reviews from the Chicago Reader, the New York Times, LA Weekly, City Limits London, Time Out London, Film Folio, and the Voice.
    - ‘Rembrandt Laughing’ by John Jost, Folio, 1988Includes critical reviews from the Chicago Reader and the Voice.
  - Cornell Cinema (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Membership Application, 1990
  - Corporation For Public Broadcasting (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Edward R. Murrow Award 1990 Nomination Information, 1989
    - Ralph Lowell Award 1990 Nomination Information, 1989
    - Call For Entries: Public Radio Program Awards, 1990
    - Call For Entries: Public Television Local Program Awards, 1990
    - CPB Informative Broadcasting Catalog,1990 (photocopied)
  - Dance (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Doris Chase Dance Series Poster
    - Merce Cunningham Dance Company Press Kit, 1991. Includes Background Information, Articles, Film and Video Articles, Performance Reviews, Film and Video Repertory
  - Deep Dish TV (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Deep Dish Directory, 1986
    - Advertisement Poster, 1987
    - Call For Tapes, 1988
    - Program Proposal Call, 1988
    - In These Times Article, ‘Free Spaces’, 1988
    - Friends of Deep Dish Newsletter, 1988
    - Advertisement Postcard,1988
    - Series Program, Fall 1990 (4 copies)
    - Program Proposal Call, 1990
    - Outweek Article ‘Dish it up’, 1990
    - Video Order form
    - Advertisement Brochure
    - Advertisement Flyer
    - Response Card
  - Digital World Conference (Distribution) (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Program Information, 1990
  - Distribution ARK Group / New ERA Media S.F. (New Age) (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - ARK Group/ New Era Media (Distribution)
    - Catalog of Visual Music, Nature, Health, and Inspirational Videos, 1990
    - An Introduction to Visual Music Video Essay
    - New Age Retailer Article, ‘New Age Visual Music Video’, 1989
    - Billboard Magazine Article, ‘Video: Inventive Couples of Sound and Vision Making Inroads at Retail’, 1988
    - The Valley Herald Article, ‘Music for the Eyes’, 1990
    - New Age Journal Article, ‘The Sight of Music’, 1990
    - ‘It’s in Every One of Us’ by Wernher Krutein, Flyer, 1989
    - ‘Illumination’ by Ken Jenkins, Flyer, 1989
    - ‘Radiance: The Experience of Light’, Flyer, 1989
  - Distribution California Newsreel (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Collision Course, booklet, 1989
    - Mapantsula, booklet, 1989
    - Black America Emerges, booklet, 1989
  - Distribution Criterion Collection (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - The Wizard of Oz postcard
    - Shock Corridor postcard
    - The Blob postcard
    - Videoscope postcard
  - Distribution – Ergo Media Video Jewish Home Entertainment (NJ) (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - A World of Jewish Home Entertainment, Catalog, 1990
  - Distribution – Direct Cinema Limited L.A. (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Films and Video Catalog
  - Distribution – First Run / Icarus Films (NY) (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Catalog of Films
    - Catalog Supplement, 1990
  - Distribution – Home Vision (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - British Video Update, brochure
    - Catalog, 1987/1988
  - Distribution – Merrimack Films (MA) (Labor Relations and Economics) (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Order Form, 1990
    - Brochure, 1990
    - Company Bios, 1990
  - Distribution – Modern Visual Communications (MVC) CA (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Index of Videos, 1988
  - Distribution – Modern Talking Picture Services NJ (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Catalog of Videos, 1987
  - Distribution - MPI Home Video (Illinois) (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - ‘The Fabulous 60’s’ brochure and order form, 1989
  - Distribution – Mystic Fire Video (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - ‘Ring of Fire’ Flyer
    - ‘On The Bowery’, Flyer
    - ‘Dog Star Man’, Flyer
    - ‘Fried Shoes, Cooked Diamonds’, Flyer
    - ‘A Gathering of Men’, Flyer
    - ‘World of Ideas’, Flyer
    - Catalog One, August 1986
    - Catalog Two
    - Catalog Three, 1990
    - Video Article, ‘Small Labels Mine Avant-Garde Diamonds’, May 1987
  - Distribution – National Video Corporation (NVC) NY (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - NVC Arts International Complete New Listing, catalog, 1986/1987
    - NVC Arts International Supplement, Spring 1987
  - Distribution – Target Video S.F. (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Video Catalog
  - Vidiots (Distribution) Santa Monica, CA (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Video Index, 1987
  - Distribution – Voyager Company (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Order Form, April 1989
    - Order Form, July 1989
    - Order Form, March 1990
    - Zulu, postcard
  - World Artists Video – Distribution (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Video Index
  - Distribution – Misc. Fusion Video (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Video Index
    - Catalog, 1988/1989
  - Documentary (general) (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - P.O.V. Season 3 Call for Entires, 1989
  - Documentary – International Documentary Association (IDA) (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - IDA Awards Documentary Competition, 1990
  - Documentary Video (LBMA) (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Retrospective of Documentary Video Catalog, Long Beach Museum of Art, 1985
  - Downtown Community Television Center, NY (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Scan Lines Calendar, May 1990
    - Scan Lines Calendar, June 1990
    - Scan Lines Calendar, Summer 1990
    - Scan Lines Calendar, September 1990
    - Scan Lines Calendar, October 1990
    - DCTV Information Flyer, 1990
    - DCTV Panel Discussion Flyer, 1990
    - Lookout Lesbian and Gay Video Festival Entry Form, 1990
    - ‘Between a Rock and a Hard Place’ Screening Schedule, 1990
    - Annual Video Festival Entry Form, 1990
    - Open Dialogue on Media Flyer, 1990
    - Call to protest Arts Censorship, 1990
    - Catalog, 1990
  - Educators for Social Responsibility (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - ESR Brochure
    - Summer Institutes for Educators Pamphlet, 1989
    - Donation Mailer, 1989
    - Donation Mailer, 1990
    - Forum Newsletter, Fall 1989
    - Publications Catalog, 1989
    - Publications Order Form, 1989
  - Electronic Arts Intermix (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Videotapes Index
    - Videotapes Index, March1990
    - Videotapes Index
    - Distribution Service Catalog, 1985
    - Order Form, 1989
  - (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Everson Museum of Art (3 Folders) (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Index of Literature
    - Jeff Perrone, “Ins and Ours of Video Artforum”, photocopied article
    - Barbara London, “ Independent Video: The First Fifteen Years”, photocopied article
    - Jonathan Price, “Video Art: A medium discovering itself”, photocopied article
    - “Man Ray, Do You Want to..”, photocopied article
    - “Chase Show Features Seattle Premiere of Video Work”, photocopied article
    - “See It Better”, photocopied article
    - Bruce Kurtz, “Popular Art and Fine Art”, photocopied article
    - Bruce Kurtz, “Artist’s Video at the Crossroads”, photocopied article
    - “Joanne Kelly: Synthesizing Dance and Video”, photocopied article
    - Russell Connor, “ The Video Window of Davidson Gigliotti”, photocopied article
    - Eric Cameron, “The Grammar of the Video Image”, photocopied article, (2 copies)
    - Electronic Arts Intermix Video Index Update, 1980
    - Index of Art and Artists from the Video Data Bank
    - Letter from Howard Wise, President of Electronic Arts Intermix
    - General Exhibition List 1969- 1974
    - Video Collection Index I
    - Video Collection Index II
  - Exercise Videos (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - The Complete Guide To Exercise Videos, Vol. 1, 1990
    - The Complete Guide To Exercise Videos, Post-Holiday Edition, 1990
    - The Complete Guide To Exercise Videos, Pre-Swimsuit Edition, 1990
    - The Complete Guide To Exercise Videos, Fall Edition, 1990
  - Experimental Television Center (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Exhibition and Residency Information
  - EZTV (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - EZTV Brochure, 1983
  - Felix: A Journal of Media Arts and Communication (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Order Form, 1990
  - Feminisim- “What Does She Want?” (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Video Data Bank Video Collection Brochure
  - Feminism- Lyn Blumenthal (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Exhibition Catalog, ‘Force of Vision’, 1989
  - Feminism Graduate Student Conference (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - 1989 Conference Schedule
    - Abstracts of Papers for Discussion, 1989
    - Slide Presentation Comments and Criticisms, 1989
  - Festival – New Angle International Video Fest. NY (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Entry application, New Angle International Video Festival, 1990
  - Festivals – Misc. (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - “Video Shorts 9,” program and guide to premiere showing, Seattle, WA, 1990
    - “30th American Film and Video Festival,” NY, registration form and information, 1988
    - “Thomas A. Edison Black Maria Film and Video Festival,” information and call for entries, 1988-1989
    - The 10th Annual Edison Black Maria Film and Video Festival,” information and call for entries, 1990
  - Film Arts Foundation (FAF) and festival notes (ind. Film and videomakers, No-Calif) (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - “Film Arts Foundation: The Northern California Organization of Independent Film and Videomakers,” informational brochure with membership application
    - “Release Print,” Film Arts Foundation newsletter, Vol. 8 no. 8, October 1990
    - “The 6th Annual Film Arts Festival,” program and schedule, 19901990
  - Film/Video Arts, Inc. NY (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - “Intermediary: A Quarterly newsletter for members of Film/Video Arts,” Vol. 7 no. 1, Fall 1990
    - Information about Electronic Arts Grants Programs
    - Catalog of courses and workshops, Autumn 1990
    - Informational brochure about membership and services
    - Includes original mailing envelope and note to Zalis from David Barker
  - Footage 89 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Promotional brochure with order reply card, 3 copies
  - Festival – Frameline, S.F. (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - “Frameline Presents,” list of feature releases for 1990
    - List of available titles
    - List of new titles in 1990
    - Includes business card and letter to Zalis from distribution manager Mark Finch
  - Franklin Furnace, N.Y. (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - 3 Postcards advertising exhibitions 1988
    - “Products and Promotion” press release, 1987
    - “The New York FLUE” newsletter, Fall 1987
    - Promotional flyer for Greeley Matt exhibit, 1988
    - “The New York FLUE” newsletter, Fall 1987
    - Promotional flyer for Billy Curmano performance, 1988
    - Poster for Teenytown, performance by Laurie Carlos, Jessical Hagedorn,Robbie McCauley
    - “International FF Flue,” newsletter, 1988
    - Invitation to Duchamp anniversary benefit, “The Avant-Garde Breaks into Midtown,” Includes original mailing envelope and RSVP card.1987
    - Receipt for back issues of “FF Flue” newsletter, 1987
    - Catalog of publications, 1977-1986
    - Poster/newsletter with general museum information and event schedules
  - Fulbright Fellowships (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - 1991-1992 information packet, including information about UK film/television exchange fellowship
  - Gallery – Ronald Feldman Fine Art, Inc. NY (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Letter to Zalis from Nadia Czap, librarian
    - List of videos by current and former gallery artists1990
    - Detailed CVs of artists Ida Applebroog, Mierle Laderman Ukeles, Hanna Wilke. 3 separate packets; includes bibliographies and exhibition histories.
  - Global Village, NY (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - “Global Village Video Study Center,” informational newletter and course catalogue, 1987
  - Guadalupe Cultural Arts Center and Tonantzin Newsletter San Antonio, TX (Chicano Arts) (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - “Guadalupe Theater CineFestival” call for entries, 1990
    - “Tonantzin,” newsletter for Chicano Arts in San Antonio, November 1987; special issue and festival program for “CineFestival Doce: The Twelfth Edition of North America’s Oldest and Largest Latino Film and Video Exhibition”1987
    - “Tonantzin,” newsletter for Chicano Arts in San Antonio, November 1988; special issue and festival program for 13th annual CineFestival 1988
    - Letter from Cindy Rios, CineFestival assistant director, regarding festival entry application terms, 1990. Includes original mailing envelope.1990
  - 83 Hallwalls (Austrian Collaboration) 7/90 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Poster and schedule for Stadtwerkstatt-TV special broadcasts on Buffalo Public Access Cable TV, 1990
    - Press release regarding broadcasts
  - Hallwalls Contemporary Arts Center Buffalo (Newsletters) (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - “Labor Intensive,” poster advertising “a series of videotapes and films examining social constructions and conditions of work”
    - Newsletter, September-October 1990
    - Newsletter, November 1990
    - Newsletter, May 1990
    - Newsletter, March 1990
    - Postcards advertising exhibitions by Ericka Beckman, John Jesurun, Barbara Bloom. Includes original mailing envelope.
    - Newsletter, May 1988
    - Newsletter, January-February 1989
    - Newsletter, November-December 1988
    - Newsletter, March 1989
    - Newsletter, April 1989
    - Newsletter, September-October 1988
    - Newsletter, January-February 1990
    - Newsletter, April 1990
    - Newsletter, November-December 1989
    - Newsletter, February 1989
    - Newsletter, May-June-July 1989, includes notes by Zalis
    - Newsletter, January 1988
    - Newsletter, September 1987
    - Mailing list information update card, 1990
  - Hallwalls (Background) (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - Newsletter, December 1986
    - Information sheet on SF Camerwork membership, 1986
    - Newsletter, March 1987
    - Newsletter, May-June 1987
    - Newsletter, September 1987
    - Newsletter, April 1988
    - Letter to Zalis from Chris Hill, January 9, 1987
    - Letter to Zalis from Edmund Cardoni, January 8, 1988
    - Packet of photocopied articles featuring Hallwalls
    - Information on exhibit, “Distant Airwaves: New Television from Europe,” May 1987. Curated by Barbara Osborn
    - “Reckoning with Retooling: Video Artists’ Relationship(s) with their Instruments, 1970’s and 80’s,” information on exhibition, March-April 1986
    - “Site-ing the Almighty: Religion and Media,” information on media program September-October 1986
    - “Dyslexic Verdicts,” information on Anthology Video Program, May 1986
    - “A Public Agenda: Priorities, Properties, and Improprieties,” information on exhibit, January 1985
    - “The Medicine Show” information on exhibit at Hallwalls and The Kitchen, 1986/1987
    - “Floating Values: A Survey of Gendered Investigations,” description of tapes in exhibit,1987. Includes promotional postcard.
    - “Floating Values: A Survey of Gendered Investigations,” photocopied program, 1987
    - Postcard advertising exhibit and artist’s talk by Mike Glier, 1988
  - Hallwalls (feminism and surveillance) (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - Zalis’ notes on video artists working with themes of feminism and surveillance
    - Press release on exhibition curated by Chris Hill, “Feeling the Faults: Confronting Dis-ease through the mediated body”
    - “Lattanzi’s Latest: An Attentional Waveform,” Chris Hill, The Squealer. Includes notes on the artist.
    - “The Medicine Show” information on exhibit at Hallwalls and The Kitchen, 1986/1987
    - “Floating Values: A Survey of Gendered Investigations,” photocopied program, 1987
    - “The Politics and Poetics of Feminism, Sexuality, and Reproductive Freedom,” poster advertising a program of video and film, September-November 1989
    - “Family Extensions: Romance, Illness, and the Economy,” photocopied program for exhibition, November-December 1987